Inventory of the Edwin Meese papers, 1941-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
- Presidential Administration of Ronald Reagan File, 1975-1991 (Boxes 554-771, 774)
  - B. 17 Geneva Conventions of 1949 revisions, 1988 (Box-folder 633: 20)
  - B. 18 Wright, Jim, ethics inquiry, 1988 (Box-folder 633: 21-22)
  - B. 19 Rashid, Mohammad Said, 1988 (Box-folder 633: 23)
  - B. 20 Defense contracting fraud investigation, 1988 (Box-folder 634: 1-8)
  - B. 21 Marcos, Ferdinand, 1988 (Box-folder 634: 9)
  - B. 22 Integrity in Post Employment Act of 1988 (Box-folder 634: 10)
  - B. 23 Coelho, Tony, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 1)
  - B. 25 Teamsters suit, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 2)
  - B. 26 Souther, Glenn M., 1988 (Box-folder 635: 3)
  - B. 27 Peoples Committee for Students of Libyan Arab Jamahariya Inc., 1988 (Box-folder 635: 4)
  - B. 28 American refugees in User, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 5)
  - B. 29 Inspector general legislation, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 6)
  - B. 30 Conn v. Conn (abortion/divorce case), 1988 (Box-folder 635: 7)
  - B. 31 Mahmoud Abed Atta (extradition case), 1988 (Box-folder 635: 8)
  - B. 32 Public safety officers benefits, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 9)
  - B. 33 Criminal Justice Leadership Conference, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 10)
  - C. 01 Assistant attorney general, Civil Division, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 11)
  - C. 02 Training specialist, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 12)
  - C. 03 Sentencing Commission, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 13)
  - C. 04 Assistant attorney general, Office of Legislative Affairs, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 14)
  - C. 06 Department of Justice staffing, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 15-17)
  - C. 07 Fifth circuit judicial nomination, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 18)
  - C. 08 Gregory, Mark, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 19)
  - C. 09 Bernott, Joan, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 20)
  - C. 10 Office of Public Affairs, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 21)
  - C. 11 Deputy attorney general, 1987 (Box-folder 635: 22)
  - C. 12 Assistant attorney general, Criminal Division, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 23)
  - C. 13 U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of California, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 24)
  - C. 14 U.S. Attorney for the Middle District of Florida, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 25)
  - C. 15 U.S. Attorney for the Middle District of Pennsylvania (Box-folder 635: 26)
  - D. 02 St. Germain, Fernand, 1988 (Box-folder 635: 27)
  - F. 01S DEA strategic planning, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 635: 28)
  - F. 01S DEA strategic planning (cont'd.), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 636: 1-2)
  - F. 02 Special Issues Coordinating Group, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 3)
  - G. 01 National Association of Attorneys General, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 4)
  - G. 02 Law Enforcement Steering CMTE, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 5)
  - G. 03 ABA Criminal Justice Section/National Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 6)
  - N. 03 Crack-violence-street gangs, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 7)
  - N. 04 Joint Chiefs of Staff Joint Committee Report on Department of Defense Support for International Drug Interdiction, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 8)
  - N. 07 Narcotics legislation, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 9)
  - N. 08 Military support of drug interdiction, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 10)
  - N. 09 DEA/FBI joint drug plan, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 11)
  - N. 10 Smoking as an addiction, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 12)
  - N. 11 National Guard support of drug enforcement, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 13)
  - N. 13 Drug czar proposals, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 14)
  - N. 14 Prevention and education, drug-free workplace, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 15)
  - N. 15 Narcotics, death penalty, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 16)
  - N. 16 International day against drug abuse and illicit trafficking, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 17)
  - N. 17 Narcotics, Bush, George, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 18)
  - N. 18 Marijuana, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 19)
  - N. 19 NDPB report, 1988 (Box-folder 636: 20)
  - KAL Flight 007 issue, 1985 (Box-folder 636: 21)
  - I/C file
    Possibly investigations/cases.
    - Abortion clinic incidents, 1986 (Box-folder 636: 22)
    - Abbas, Abul, 1986 (Box-folder 636: 23)
    - Archille Lauro hijacking, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 636: 24)
    - Alabama voter fraud cases (election of 4 September 1985), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 636: 25)
    - Albertson v. U.S. (state secrets privilege claim), 1986 (Box-folder 636: 26)
    - Arafat, Yassir, 1986 (Box-folder 637: 1-2)
    - Artwork recovered from France, 1988 (Box-folder 637: 3)
    - Baker Intl Corp-Hughes Tool Company merger proposal, 1987 (Box-folder 637: 4)
    - Bolivia operation, 1986 July 17 (Box-folder 637: 5)
    - Bork nomination, 1987 (Box-folder 637: 6)
    - Camarena, Enrique (murdered DEA agent), 1988 (Box-folder 637: 7)
    - Chinese diplomats expelled for espionage, 1987 (Box-folder 637: 8)
    - Command Center daily incident summaries, 1986 (Box-folder 637: 9)
    - Cortez, Victor (assault on federal officer), 1986 August (Box-folder 637: 10)
    - Cuban political prisoners, 1986 (Box-folder 637: 11)
    - Daniloff, USSR hostage incident, 1986 September (Box-folder 637: 12)
    - D.C. government investigation, 1988 (Box-folder 637: 13)
    - D.C. prison situation, 1988 (Box-folder 637: 14)
    - Deaver investigation, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 637: 15-17)
    - Demjanjuk, John, 1988 (Box-folder 638: 1)
    - Detroit newspaper legal case, 1988 (Box-folder 638: 2-4)
    - Discotheque bombing, West Berlin, 1986 April 5 (Box-folder 638: 5)
    - E. F. Hutton, 1987 (Box-folder 638: 6)
    - El Rukn street gang prosecution, 1986 October (Box-folder 638: 7)
    - El Salvador terrorist attack, 1985 June (Box-folder 638: 8)
    - Environmental Protection Agency controversy, House Judiciary Committee inquiry, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 638: 9-11)
    - Environmental Protection Agency controversy, House Judiciary Committee inquiry (cont'd.), 1986-1988 (Box-folder 639: 1)
    - Espionage charge against Marine Guards/U.S. Embassy, Moscow, 1987 February (Box-folder 639: 2)
    - Farrakhan, Louis, 1986 April (Box-folder 639: 3)
    - FBI, Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), 1988 (Box-folder 639: 4)
    - First English Evangelical Lutheran Church of Glendale v. County of Los Angeles (Supreme Court), 1986 (Box-folder 639: 5)
    - Friedland, David, fugitive apprehended by FBI, 1987 (Box-folder 639: 6)
    - Fujitsu acquisition of interest in Fairchild Semiconductor, 1986 November (Box-folder 639: 7)
    - Ghandi, demonstrations against the prime minister, 1985 June 11-12 (Box-folder 639: 8)
    - Ginsburg, Douglas, Supreme Court nominee, 1987 (Box-folder 639: 9)
    - Hamadei, Mohammed Ali (TWA 847 hijacking suspect), 1987 January 20 (Box-folder 639: 11)
    - Harris, Vinson investigation, 1986 (Box-folder 639: 12)
    - Howard, Edward Lee case, 1986 June (Box-folder 639: 13)
    - Huntsman, James, kidnap victim rescued by FBI agent, 1987 (Box-folder 639: 14)
    - Iran situation, 1986 November (Box-folder 639: 15)
    - Iraqi pipeline inquiry, 1988 (Box-folder 639: 16)
    - Kane, Arthur, incident involving brokerage dealer in Witness Protection Program, 1987 (Box-folder 639: 17)
    - Karamba, Terrence, custody dispute of abused son of Zimbabwean diplomat, 1988 (Box-folder 640: 1)
    - Katkov, Mikhail, Soviet diplomat expelled for espionage, 1987 December (Box-folder 640: 2)
    - Kennedy, Anthony M., nomination to the Supreme Court, 1987 November 11 (Box-folder 640: 3)
    - Kennedy, Anthony M., Supreme Court nominee, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 640: 4-6)
    - Kennedy, Anthony, clippings, nomination to Supreme Court, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 640: 7-8)
    - Lara, Patricia (Columbian journalist denied entry), 1987 (Box-folder 640: 9)
    - Libyan terrorism, 1986 April (Box-folder 640: 10)
    - Linnas, Karl, 1987 (Box-folder 640: 11-12)
    - Marcos situation, 1986 February 28 (Box-folder 640: 13)
    - McDonald, et al v. County of Yolo, et al, U.S. Support, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 641: 1)
    - Mengele case, 1985 (Box-folder 641: 2)
    - Mexican border shooting, 1987 (Box-folder 641: 3)
    - Mexico situation (Von Raab comments), 1986 May (Box-folder 641: 4)
    - Moon, Reverend Sun Myung, 1985 (Box-folder 641: 5)
    - Nipon, Albert, recommendations for transfer to halfway house, 1986 October (Box-folder 641: 6)
    - Nofziger, Lyn, investigation into alleged violation of conflict-of-interest laws, 1988 (Box-folder 641: 7)
    - Norml v. Mullen (California marijuana eradication case), 1986 April 1 (Box-folder 641: 8)
    - Omni International Corporation case, 1986 May 19 (Box-folder 641: 9)
    - Operation Closing Bell, 1987 April 16 (Box-folder 641: 10)
    - Operation Golden Rod, 1987 (Box-folder 641: 11)
    - Owen, Conan, 1988 (Box-folder 641: 12)
    - Pacific Southwest Airlines flight 1771 crash, 1987 December 7 (Box-folder 641: 13)
    - Panama, economic sanctions, 1988 (Box-folder 641: 14)
    - Philadelphia police corruption investigation, 1985 August (Box-folder 641: 15)
    - Pierce, Julian, 1988 March (Box-folder 641: 16)
    - Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO)–U.S. effort to force closing of UN mission office (Box-folder 641: 17)
    - Popular front for the liberation of Palestine, 1987 (Box-folder 641: 18)
    - Pornography Commission litigation, 1987 (Box-folder 641: 19)
    - Presser, Jackie, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 641: 20)
    - Prison disturbances; Oakdale, Louisiana, and Atlanta, Georgia, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 642: 1-8)
    - Prison disturbances, FBI after action review, 1988 (Box-folder 642: 9)
    - Prisoner escape from FCI, Pleasanton, California, 1986 November 5 (Box-folder 642: 10)
    - Rochon, Donald, FBI agent discrimination case, 1988 (Box-folder 643: 1)
    - Rockwell International Corporation (defense procurement fraud), 1988 (Box-folder 643: 2)
    - Romanian Seaman case (Stephan Vranea), 1985 November 6 (Box-folder 643: 3)
    - Sanctuary cases, 1986 (Box-folder 643: 4)
    - Scranage, Sharon Anne, 1985 July (Box-folder 643: 5)
    - U.S. v. Eugenio Silva et al/Arms Export Control Act (re Anita Castello), 1986 (Box-folder 643: 6)
    - Soviet hostage-taking, 1986 October (Box-folder 643: 7)
    - Soviet Seaman case (Miroslav Medvid), 1985 October 24 (Box-folder 643: 8)
    - Space shuttle Challenger accident, 1986 January 28 (Box-folder 643: 9)
    - Special MIA Mission, 1986 September (Box-folder 643: 10)
    - Texaco/Pennzoil, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 643: 11)
    - TWA flight 840 bombing (Rome to Athens), 1986 April 2 (Box-folder 643: 12)
    - Unauthorized disclosure of information re Libya, 1986 October 2 (Box-folder 643: 13)
    - Walker espionage case, 1985 June (Box-folder 643: 14)
    - Wedtech, 1987 (Box-folder 643: 15)
    - Waldheim, Kurt, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 643: 16-20)
    - Whittlesey, Faith, inquiry, 1986 September (Box-folder 644: 1)
    - Younis, Fawaz, apprehension of Lebanese terrorist, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 644: 2)
    - Zakharov, Gennady (espionage, USSR), 1986 September (Box-folder 644: 3)
  - Alphabetical file
    - Administrative Conference of the United States, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 644: 4)
    - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of United States Attorneys (AGAC), 1988 (Box-folder 644: 5)
    - Air Force Academy, undated (Box-folder 644: 6)
    - American Bar Association, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 644: 7)
    - American Bar Association, Standing Committee on Law and National Security, 1987 (Box-folder 644: 8)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, undated (Box-folder 644: 9)
    - American Enterprise Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 644: 10)
    - American Law Institute, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 644: 11)
    - American Medical Association, 1986 (Box-folder 644: 12)
    - American Society for Industrial Security, 1986 (Box-folder 644: 13)
    - Antitrust Division, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 644: 14)
    - Associate Attorney General, 1986 (Box-folder 644: 15)
    - Asylum Policy and Review Unit, 1987 (Box-folder 644: 16)
    - Beverly Hills Bar Association Journal (Robert Aronoff, editor), 1985 (Box-folder 644: 17)
    - Border Patrol, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 644: 18)
    - Bureau of Justice Assistance, 1988 (Box-folder 644: 19)
    - BJS (Bureau of Justice Statistics), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 645: 1-2)
    - CATO Institute, 1986 (Box-folder 645: 3)
    - Center for Judicial Studies, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 645: 4)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1987 (Box-folder 645: 5)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1985 (Box-folder 645: 6)
    - Citizens for America, 1986 (Box-folder 645: 7)
    - Civil Division, organization and functions, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 645: 8)
    - Civil Rights Commission, 1988 (Box-folder 645: 9)
    - Civil Rights Division, 1987 (Box-folder 645: 10)
    - Coast Guard, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 645: 11)
    - Community Relations Service, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 645: 12)
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1988 (Box-folder 645: 13)
    - Criminal Division, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 645: 14)
    - CSIS (Center for Strategic and International Studies), undated (Box-folder 645: 15)
    - Customs Service, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 645: 16)
    - Department of Justice, 1988 (Box-folder 646: 1)
    - Department of Justice, organization and procedures, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 646: 2)
    - Department of Labor, 1988 (Box-folder 646: 3)
    - District of Columbia courts, 1987 (Box-folder 646: 4)
    - Department of Defense, Office of Assistant Secretary of Defense (Reserve Affairs), undated (Box-folder 646: 5)
    - Drug Enforcement Agency, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 646: 6-7)
    - Economic crime control, 1986 (Box-folder 646: 8)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, Clarence Pendleton, 1987 (Box-folder 646: 9)
    - Executive Office of U.S. Attorneys, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 646: 10-12)
    - Executive Secretariat, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 646: 13)
    - FAA (Federal Aviation Administration), 1987 (Box-folder 647: 1)
    - FBI/Butte, 1987 (Box-folder 647: 2)
    - Federal Executive Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 647: 3)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 647: 4)
    - Eye Dentify, Inc., 1986 (Box-folder 647: 5)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, Ed Gray, 1987 (Box-folder 647: 6)
    - Federalist Society, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 647: 7)
    - Federal Justice Research Program, 1985 (Box-folder 647: 8)
    - Federal Prison Industries, Inc. (UNICOR), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 647: 9)
    - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 647: 10)
    - U.S. Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court (FISA Court), 1985 (Box-folder 647: 11)
    - Fraternal Order of Police, 1988 (Box-folder 647: 12)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 647: 13-17)
    - General Services Administration, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 648: 1)
    - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1987 (Box-folder 648: 2)
    - Guatemala, 1986 (Box-folder 648: 3)
    - Heritage Foundation, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 648: 4)
    - Honolulu Police Department, 1987 (Box-folder 648: 5)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 648: 6-8)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service, Ellis Island proposal (Box-folder 648: 9)
    - Information Security Oversight Office, 1987 (Box-folder 648: 10)
    - Institute for Government and Politics, 1988 (Box-folder 648: 11)
    - Institute of Judicial Administration, 1987 (Box-folder 648: 12)
    - International Association of Chiefs of Police, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 648: 13)
    - International Criminal Investigative Training Assistance Program (ICITAP), 1986-1988 (Box-folder 648: 14)
    - Department of the Interior, 1985 (Box-folder 648: 15)
    - Interpol, 1985 (Box-folder 648: 16)
    - Justice Command Center, 1987 (Box-folder 648: 17)
    - Justice Department statutes, undated (Box-folder 648: 18)
    - Justice Management Division, 1987 (Box-folder 649: 1)
    - Office of Justice programs, 1986 (Box-folder 649: 2)
    - Office of Juvenile Justice Delinquency Prevention (OJJDP), 1985-1987 (Box-folder 649: 3)
    - Lands and Natural Resources, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 649: 4)
    - Los Angeles Police Department (LAPD), 1986 (Box-folder 649: 5)
    - Office of Legal Counsel, summaries of new matters, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 649: 6)
    - Office of Legal Counsel, 1985 (Box-folder 649: 7)
    - Office of Legal Policy, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 649: 8-10)
    - Legal Services Corporation, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 649: 11)
    - Office of Legislative Affairs, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 650: 1-3)
    - Office of Liaison Services, 1986 (Box-folder 650: 4)
    - League of United Latin American Citizens (LULAC), 1985 (Box-folder 650: 5)
    - U.S. Marshals Service, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 650: 6)
    - Merit Systems Protection Board, 1988 (Box-folder 650: 7)
    - Mexico, 1987 (Box-folder 650: 8)
    - NASA, 1986 (Box-folder 650: 9)
    - National Academy of Corrections, 1986 (Box-folder 650: 10)
    - National Association of Attorneys General, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 650: 11)
    - National Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers, 1987 (Box-folder 650: 12)
    - National Criminal Justice Association, 1986 (Box-folder 650: 13)
    - National District Attorneys Association, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 650: 14)
    - National Institute of Corrections, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 650: 15)
    - National Institute of Justice, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 650: 16)
    - National Law Enforcement Officers' Memorial Fund, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 650: 17)
    - National Lawyers Guild, 1987 (Box-folder 651: 1)
    - National Legal Center for the Public Interest, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 651: 2)
    - National Obscenity Enforcement Unit, 1988 (Box-folder 651: 3)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 1985 (Box-folder 651: 4)
    - National Organization of Black Law Enforcement Executives (NOBLE), 1986 (Box-folder 651: 5)
    - National Rifle Association, 1988 (Box-folder 651: 6)
    - National Security Council, 1985 (Box-folder 651: 7)
    - National Sheriffs' Association, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 651: 8)
    - Naval Investigative Service, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 651: 9)
    - Navy, 1986 (Box-folder 651: 10)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1987 (Box-folder 651: 11)
    - Office of Government Ethics, 1987 (Box-folder 651: 12)
    - Office of Justice Programs, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 651: 13)
    - Office of Policy Development (White House), 1986 (Box-folder 651: 14)
    - Office of Professional Responsibility, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 651: 15)
    - Office of Special Investigations, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 651: 16)
    - Organized Crime Drug Enforcement Task Force (OCDETF), 1985 (Box-folder 651: 17)
    - Pacific Legal Foundation, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 651: 18)
    - Parole Commission, 1987 (Box-folder 651: 19)
    - Pardon Attorney, 1987 (Box-folder 651: 20)
    - People for the American Way, 1986 (Box-folder 651: 21)
    - Pepperdine University, 1986 (Box-folder 651: 22)
    - Police Executive Research Forum, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 651: 23)
    - Police Foundation, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 651: 24)
    - Personnel, Department of Justice, 1985 (Box-folder 651: 25)
    - Police Organizations, 1986 (Box-folder 651: 26)
    - Pornography Commission, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 651: 27)
    - President's Commission on Executive Exchange (Box-folder 651: 28)
    - President's Commission on Organized Crime, 1986 (Box-folder 652: 1)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 652: 2-3)
    - Office of Public Affairs, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 652: 4-5)
    - Public Integrity Section, 1985 (Box-folder 652: 6)
    - Research and Development Review Board (DOJ), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 652: 7)
    - San Diego County Bar Association, 1986 (Box-folder 652: 8)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1987 (Box-folder 652: 9)
    - Senior Executives Association, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 652: 10)
    - Solicitor General, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 652: 11)
    - Southern California Edison, undated (Box-folder 652: 12)
    - State Justice Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 652: 13)
    - Supreme Court, 1987 (Box-folder 652: 14)
    - Tax Division, 1985 (Box-folder 652: 15)
    - United Nations, 1985 (Box-folder 652: 16)
    - United States Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy, 1986 (Box-folder 652: 17)
    - United States Attorneys, 1987 (Box-folder 652: 18)
    - U.S. Trustees, 1988 (Box-folder 652: 19)
    - Veterans Administration, 1988 (Box-folder 652: 20)
    - White House Conference for a Drug Free America, 1987 (Box-folder 652: 21)
    - White House Fellows Program, 1985 (Box-folder 652: 22)
    - Young American Medals Program, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 652: 23)
  - Speech material, alphabetical file
    - Abortion, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 652: 24)
    - Administration accomplishments, 1982 (Box-folder 653: 1)
    - Affirmative action, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 2)
    - AIDS, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 653: 3-4)
    - Alternative dispute resolution, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 5)
    - Antitrust, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 653: 6)
    - Arms control and nuclear weapons policy, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 653: 7)
    - Attorneys' fees, 1985 (Box-folder 653: 8)
    - Aviation, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 9)
    - Bail and pre-trial detention, 1986 (Box-folder 653: 10)
    - Bibliography, 1985 (Box-folder 653: 11)
    - Budget of Federal Government, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 653: 12)
    - Budget process, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 653: 13)
    - Cabinet government, 1985 (Box-folder 653: 14)
    - Cabinet system, 1985 (Box-folder 653: 15)
    - CCMA (government computerization program), 1985 (Box-folder 653: 16)
    - Capitalism, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 17)
    - Child abuse, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 18)
    - China, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 19)
    - Citizenship, 1985 (Box-folder 653: 20)
    - Civil rights, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 653: 21)
      Includes Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action materials.
    - Conference facilities, undated (Box-folder 653: 22)
    - Congressional ethics, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 653: 23)
    - Counterintelligence, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 24)
    - Crime, computer, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 25)
    - Crime control, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 26)
    - Crime, economic, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 27)
    - Crime prevention programs, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 653: 28)
    - Crime and public opinion, 1987 (Box-folder 653: 29)
    - Crime, white collar, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 653: 30)
    - Criminal justice, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 654: 1-3)
    - Defamation, 1987 (Box-folder 654: 4)
    - Defense, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 654: 5)
      Includes military affairs materials.
    - Demographic data, 1983 (Box-folder 654: 6)
    - Department of Justice, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 654: 7)
    - Deregulation, undated (Box-folder 654: 8)
    - Economic regulation, undated (Box-folder 654: 9)
    - Education, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 654: 10)
    - Election, 1987 (Box-folder 654: 11)
    - Electronic surveillance, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 654: 12)
    - Emergency number, 1987 (Box-folder 654: 13)
    - Espionage, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 654: 14)
    - Ethics, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 654: 15)
    - Ethics, George Bush, 1988 (Box-folder 654: 16)
    - Fairness doctrine, 1987 (Box-folder 654: 17)
    - Federal compensation, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 654: 18)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1985 (Box-folder 654: 19)
    - Federal government organization, 1984 (Box-folder 654: 20)
    - Firearms, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 654: 21)
    - Fiscal policy, 1984 (Box-folder 654: 22)
    - Foreign affairs, 1984 (Box-folder 654: 23)
    - Foreign Registration Act of 1938 (Box-folder 654: 24)
    - Foreign counterintelligence, 1985 (Box-folder 655: 1)
    - Forfeiture of assets, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 655: 2)
    - Fraud, waste, misuse of government funds, 1986 (Box-folder 655: 3)
    - Fugitives, 1987 (Box-folder 655: 4)
    - Hunger, 1985 (Box-folder 655: 5)
    - President's Council on Integrity and Efficiency, speech material, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 655: 6-7)
    - Historical issues and projects, 1985 (Box-folder 655: 8)
    - Judicial corruption, 1986 (Box-folder 655: 9)
    - Judicial misconduct and disability, 1986 (Box-folder 655: 10)
    - Judicial selection, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 655: 11-12)
    - Judicial system, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 655: 13-14)
    - Juvenile crime, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 655: 15)